Registrar, Office of the; Records ua530
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Office of the Registrar Records
1900-2016
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
State University of New York at Albany. Office of the Registrar
ua530
57.33 cubic ft. 8 Digital Files
Contains student transcripts and the official schedule of classes and academic calendar.
Administrative History
The Registrars Office is responsible for registration related activities, the Universitys academic calendar, issuance of official transcripts, awarding of degrees, the schedule of classes, grading, and administration of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA), and other matters of record.
Scope and Contents
Contains student transcripts from 1900 until about 1987, the official schedule of classes, web archives of the registrar's website, and some additional administrative records.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is arranged in to 8 topical series.
Acquisition Information
All items in this collection were transferred to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives.
Access
Access to the Web Archives and the Schedule of Classes is unrestricted.
This collection contains student records which are governed by the New York Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA). We are not legally able to provide access to the restricted records in this collection. Please consult an archivist for more details.
If you are a current or former student and need a copy of your transcript, please contact the Office of the Registrar.
College administrators; Higher Education--Administration; Digital Files; UAlbany Academic Administration; State University of New York at Albany; Milne School; State University of New York at Albany. Graduate School of Public Affairs
- Web Archives, 2000 August 17-2016 June 3; 1; 1 Web-Archive
  Scope and Contents
  Web crawling is managed through the Internet Archive's Archive-It service. This page includes links to both the university's collection and the Internet Archive's public collection.
  Surface-level crawling of www.albany.edu is performed daily which chould include most top-level webpages. Separate targeted crawls are performed monthly or quarterly attempt to gather all content.
  - http://www.albany.edu/registrar/ - University Archives collection, 2013 May 8-present
  - http://www.albany.edu/registrar/ - Internet Archive collection, 2000 August 17-2016 June 3
- Transcripts, 1900-1917; 2; 1 cubic ft.
  Conditions Governing Access
  This series contains student records which are governed by the New York Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA). We are not legally able to provide access to these records. Please consult an archivist for more details.
  Student transcripts from the New York State Normal College and the State College for Teachers.
- Transcripts, 1918-1955; 3; 14 cubic ft.
  Student Transcripts of the New York State College for Teachers.
- Transcripts, ca. 1956-1987; 4; 38 cubic ft.
  Student Transcripts from the New York State College for Teachers and the State University of New York at Albany.
- Milne School Transcripts, ca. 1941-1976; 5; 1.67 cubic ft.
  Transcripts of the Milne School, the teacher training high school administered by the State College for Teachers and then the State University of New York at Albany.
- Graduate School of Public Affairs Transcripts, ca. 1962-1967; 6; .67 cubic ft.
  Student transcripts. The Graduate School was originally a pivate school jointly administered by New York University and Syracuse University. Starting in 1960, the school began to recived public aid and became part of the State University of New York at Albany in 1966. Now known as the Nelson A. Rockefeller College of Public Affairs and Policy.
- Schedule of Classes, 1952-2006; 7; 1 cubic ft. 8 Digital Files
  - Schedule of Classes, 1952 (Box 1 (7-Schedule of Classes), Folder 1)
  - Schedule of Classes, 1953 (Box 1 (7-Schedule of Classes), Folder 2)
  - Schedule of Classes, 1959 (Box 1 (7-Schedule of Classes), Folder 3)
  - Schedule of Classes, 1960 (Box 1 (7-Schedule of Classes), Folder 4)
  - Schedule of Classes, 1961 (Box 1 (7-Schedule of Classes), Folder 5)
  - Schedule of Classes, 1962 (Box 1 (7-Schedule of Classes), Folder 6)
  - Schedule of Classes, 1963 (Box 1 (7-Schedule of Classes), Folder 7)
  - Schedule of Classes, 1964 (Box 1 (7-Schedule of Classes), Folder 8)
  - Schedule of Classes, 1965 (Box 1 (7-Schedule of Classes), Folder 9)
  - Schedule of Classes, 1966 (Box 1 (7-Schedule of Classes), Folder 10)
  - Schedule of Classes, 1967 (Box 1 (7-Schedule of Classes), Folder 11)
  - Schedule of Classes, 1968 (Box 1 (7-Schedule of Classes), Folder 12)
  - Schedule of Classes, 1969 (Box 1 (7-Schedule of Classes), Folder 13)
  - Schedule of Classes, 1970 (Box 1 (7-Schedule of Classes), Folder 14)
  - Schedule of Classes, 1971 (Box 1 (7-Schedule of Classes), Folder 15)
  - Schedule of Classes, 1972 (Box 1 (7-Schedule of Classes), Folder 16)
  - Schedule of Classes, 1973 (Box 1 (7-Schedule of Classes), Folder 17)
  - Schedule of Classes, 1974 (Box 2 (7-Schedule of Classes), Folder 1)
  - Schedule of Classes, 1975 (Box 2 (7-Schedule of Classes), Folder 2)
  - Schedule of Classes, 1976 (Box 2 (7-Schedule of Classes), Folder 3)
  - Schedule of Classes, 1977 (Box 2 (7-Schedule of Classes), Folder 4)
  - Schedule of Classes, 1978 (Box 2 (7-Schedule of Classes), Folder 5)
  - Schedule of Classes, 1979 (Box 2 (7-Schedule of Classes), Folder 6)
  - Schedule of Classes, 1980 (Box 2 (7-Schedule of Classes), Folder 7)
  - Schedule of Classes, 1981 (Box 2 (7-Schedule of Classes), Folder 8)
  - Schedule of Classes, 1982 (Box 2 (7-Schedule of Classes), Folder 9)
  - Schedule of Classes, 1983 (Box 2 (7-Schedule of Classes), Folder 10)
  - Schedule of Classes, 1984 (Box 2 (7-Schedule of Classes), Folder 11)
  - Schedule of Classes, 1985 (Box 3 (7-Schedule of Classes), Folder 1)
  - Schedule of Classes, 1986 (Box 3 (7-Schedule of Classes), Folder 2)
  - Schedule of Classes, 1987 (Box 3 (7-Schedule of Classes), Folder 3)
  - Schedule of Classes, 1988 (Box 3 (7-Schedule of Classes), Folder 4)
  - Schedule of Classes, 1989 (Box 3 (7-Schedule of Classes), Folder 5)
  - Schedule of Classes, 1990 (Box 3 (7-Schedule of Classes), Folder 6)
  - Schedule of Classes, 1991 (Box 3 (7-Schedule of Classes), Folder 7)
  - Schedule of Classes, 1992 (Box 3 (7-Schedule of Classes), Folder 8)
  - Schedule of Classes, 1993 (Box 3 (7-Schedule of Classes), Folder 9)
  - Schedule of Classes, 1994 (Box 4 (7-Schedule of Classes), Folder 1)
  - Schedule of Classes, 1995 (Box 4 (7-Schedule of Classes), Folder 2)
  - Schedule of Classes, 1996 (Box 4 (7-Schedule of Classes), Folder 3)
  - Schedule of Classes, 1997 (Box 4 (7-Schedule of Classes), Folder 4)
  - Schedule of Classes, 1998 (Box 4 (7-Schedule of Classes), Folder 5)
  - Schedule of Classes, 1999 (Box 4 (7-Schedule of Classes), Folder 6)
  - Schedule of Classes, 2000 (Box 4 (7-Schedule of Classes), Folder 7)
  - Schedule of Classes, 2001 (Box 4 (7-Schedule of Classes), Folder 8)
  - Schedule of Classes, 2002 (Box 4 (7-Schedule of Classes), Folder 9)
  - Schedule of Classes, 2003 (Box 4 (7-Schedule of Classes), Folder 10)
  - Schedule of Classes, 2004 (Box 4 (7-Schedule of Classes), Folder 11)
  - Schedule of Classes, 2005 (Box 4 (7-Schedule of Classes), Folder 12)
  - Eight Week Two Quarter Courses, 2005 (Box 4 (7-Schedule of Classes), Folder 13)
  - Schedule of Classes, 2006 (Box 4 (7-Schedule of Classes), Folder 14)
  - Schedule of Classes, 2015 Winter
  - Schedule of Classes, 2016 Spring
  - Schedule of Classes, 2016 Summer
  - Schedule of Classes, 2016 Fall
  - Schedule of Classes, 2017 Winter
  - Schedule of Classes, 2017 Spring
  - Schedule of Classes, 2017 Summer
  - Schedule of Classes, 2017 Fall
- Subject Files, ca. 1960-1988; 8; 1 cubic ft.
  Portions of this series contain student records which are governed by the New York Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA). We are not legally able to provide access to the restricted records in this series. Please consult an archivist for more details.
  Arrangement
  Ordered alphabetically.
  Additional administrative records.